{"data":[{"question":"Is this your pencil? No, it isn't. It's ________ pencil.","a":"my","b":"her","c":"our","d":"hers","answer":"2","explain":"- Her ( possessive determiner) + N","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"________ parents are workers.","a":"We","b":"They","c":"Our","d":"I","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use our as a possessive determiner + noun\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"This is my new shirt. - Oh, ________ color is pretty.","a":"it","b":"its","c":"their","d":"they","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Its: used as a possessive determiner; its color = my new shirt's color\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"He is ________ engineer.","a":"an","b":"a","c":"the","d":"no article","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use a\/ an when you say what somebody's job","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Your sister is a student and his sister is a student, ________.","a":"both","b":"also","c":"and","d":"too","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Too: used at the end of a sentence or clause to mean \"also\".","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"My brother is 6.68 m ________.","a":"short","b":"tall","c":"taller","d":"shorter","answer":"2","explain":"\n-\u00a0Five inches\/feet\/metres\/yards etc tall: used for talking about measurements of height\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"My mother is 32 and my father is 43. My mother is younger ________ My father.","a":"than","b":"as","c":"but","d":"and","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use the comparative form of short adjective (young)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"I am ________ teacher.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When mentioning career of someone, we say: he\/she... is a\/an + career.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"My uncle is ________ good engineer.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When mentioning career of someone, we say: he\/she... is a\/an + career.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"That is ________ eraser.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A\/an + singular noun. Eraser begins with vowel \"a\" so we use an\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}